http://www.runtime.com/privacy-policy

Skip to main content
Main navigationAbout UsAbout UsOur ApproachOur ResponsibilityPrivacy PolicyServicesProduct DesignArchitecture and DevelopmentAgility and ToolingBusiness GrowthSuccess storiesHealthcareAutomotiveFintechOther DomainsIndustriesHealthcareAutomotiveFintechBlogCareersContactsAbout UsOur ApproachOur ResponsibilityPrivacy PolicyPrivacy Policy
Your privacy is important to us
It is Archer Software's policy to respect your privacy regarding any information we may collect from you across our website, https://archer-soft.com, and other sites we own and operate.We only ask for personal information when we truly need it to provide a service to you. We collect it by fair and lawful means, with your knowledge and consent. We also let you know why we’re collecting it and how it will be used.We only retain collected information for as long as necessary to provide you with your requested service. What data we store, we’ll protect within commercially acceptable means to prevent loss and theft, as well as unauthorized access, disclosure, copying, use or modification.We don’t share any personally identifying information publicly or with third-parties, except when required to by law.Our website may link to external sites that are not operated by us. Please be aware that we have no control over the content and practices of these sites, and cannot accept responsibility or liability for their respective privacy policies.You are free to refuse our request for your personal information, with the understanding that we may be unable to provide you with some of your desired services.Please, feel free to reach out with any questions about your personal data we collect and store to Kyryll Shcherbyna, Archer's Data Protection Officer at: dpo@archer-soft.com.Your continued use of our website will be regarded as an acceptance of our practices around privacy and personal information. If you have any questions about how we handle user data and personal information, feel free to contact us.This policy is effective as of 1 January 2020.Hire UsFirst nameLast nameEmailPhoneCompany nameLeave your commentProduct Lifecycle stage- None -New IdeaProduct GrowthProduct SupportProduct RedesignProduct DevelopmentBusiness AnalysisSystem AnalysisProduct MaintenanceStaffingHelp DeskLocalizationArcher Software needs the contact information you provide to contact you about our products and services.You may unsubsribe from these communications at any time.
